[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":37605,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":132990,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure th at when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":3717,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":136709,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":5063,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":141774,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1679,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":143454,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2926,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":146381,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1080,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":147461,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second  one to  it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2640,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":150102,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1303,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":151405,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":19121,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":170526,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":950,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":171477,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2024,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":173501,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6 </sub> 0  = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":871,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":174373,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":2072,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":176445,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":727,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":177173,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><b r /> (Re member, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3","4"],"rt":2840,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":180013,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":856,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":180869,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your res ult.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":1910,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":182781,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":728,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":183509,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":1968,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":185478,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":741,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":186221,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":1624,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":187845,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":725,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":188571,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":5863,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":194436,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse  under + <sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":9600,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":204036,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":2776,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":206812,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":832,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":207644,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br / > (Remem ber, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":1807,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":209452,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":616,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":210068,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":1528,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":211596,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":592,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":212188,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":1512,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":213700,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6 </sub>.","rt":624,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":214324,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":1776,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":216100,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2175,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":218276,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be perf ormed st arting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":16088,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":234364,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but  there is  no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":21504,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":255868,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":4311,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":260180,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1111,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":261292,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remembe r, a gen erator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":23936,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":285228,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":865,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":286093,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember , a gene rator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":8485,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":294580,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":864,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":295444,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":2374,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":297819,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1064,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":298884,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the n ew opera tion. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":3695,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":302579,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2656,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":305236,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":607,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":305843,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":14529,"trial_type":" question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":320373,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":2312,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":322685,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":1967,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":324653,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":1815,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":326469,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["34","3"],"rt":2896,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":329365,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":1032,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":330397,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Pleas e explai n in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"Add 4 and 1 together to receive 5. Is 5 less than 9? Yes, it is, so we do not need to moduli it over 9.","explanation_history":["Add 4 and 1 together to receive 5. Is 5 less than 9 ","Add 4 and 1 together to receive 5. Is 5 less than 9? Yes, it is, so wwe do ","Add 4 and 1 together to receive 5. Is 5 less than 9? Yes, it is, so wwe do","Add 4 and 1 together to receive 5. Is 5 less than 9? Yes, it is, so wwe d","Add 4 and 1 together to receive 5. Is 5 less than 9? Yes, it is, so wwe ","Add 4 and 1 together to receive 5. Is 5 less than 9? Yes, it is, so wwe","Add 4 and 1 together to receive 5. Is 5 less than 9? Yes, it is, so ww","Add 4 and 1 together to receive 5. Is 5 less than 9? Yes, it is, so we do not tn","Add 4 and 1 together to receive 5. Is 5 less than 9? Yes, it is, so we do not t","Add 4 and 1 together to receive 5. Is  5 less  than 9? Yes, it is, so we do not need to moduli it over 9."],"response_history":["5"],"rt":29199,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":359597,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"Add 8 and 4 together to receive 12. Is 12 greater than 9? Yes, it is, so we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3.","explanation_history":["8","Add 8 and 4 together to receive 12. IS 1","Add 8 and 4 together to receive 12. IS ","Add 8 and 4 together to receive 12. IS","Add 8 and 4 together to receive 12. Is 12 greater than 9? Yes, it is, so we sub","Add 8 and 4 together to receive 12. Is 12 greater than 9? Yes, it is, so we su","Add 8 and 4 together to receive 12. Is 12 greater than 9? Yes, it is, so we s","Add 8 and 4 together to receive 12. Is 12 greater than 9? Yes, i t is, so  we subtract 9 from 19","Add 8 and 4 together to receive 12. Is 12 greater than 9? Yes, it is, so we subtract 9 from 12 to get 3."],"response_history":["12","1","3"],"rt":24285,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":383883,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"0 is always the identity of modular addition","explanation_history":["0 is always the identity of modular arti","0 is always the identity of modular art","0 is always the identity of modular ar","0 is always the identity of modular a","0 is always the identity of modular addition"],"response_history":["0"],"rt":59856,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":443740,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the invers e of 5 u nder +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":5972,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":449715,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":2721,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":452437,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2429,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":454867,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"3 + ? = 0 = 9, then ? = 9 - 3, so we see that ? = 6","explanation_history":["What","Wha","Wh","W","3 + ? = 0 udner +9","3 + ? = 0 udner +","3 + ? = 0 udner ","3 + ? = 0 udner","3 + ? = 0 udne","3 + ? = 0 udn","3 + ? = 0 ud","3 + ? = 0 under + 9","3 + ? = 0 under + ","3 + ? = 0 under +9?","3 + ? = 0 u","3 + ? = 0 = 9, then 3 ","3 + ? = 0 = 9, then 3","3 + ? = 0 = 9, then ? = 9 -3 ","3 + ? = 0 = 9, then ? = 9 -3","3 + ? = 0 = 9, then ? = 9 - 3, ","3 + ? = 0 = 9, then ? = 9 - 3,","3 + ? = 0 = 9, then ? = 9 - 3 s","3 + ? = 0 = 9, then ? = 9 - 3 ","3 + ? = 0 = 9, then ? = 9 - 3, so we see that ? = 6"],"response_history":["6"],"rt":36232,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":491100,"internal_chunk_id":"0- 0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"If I continue to add 2 to itself under 9, can I get every whole number? 2, 4, 6, 8, 1, 3, 5, 7, 0. Yes, I can","explanation_history":["If I a","If I continue to add 2 to istea","If I continue to add 2 to iste","If I continue to add 2 to ist","If I continue to add 2 to is","If I continue to add 2 to itself udner 9","If I continue to add 2 to itself udner ","If I continue to add 2 to itself udner","If I continue to add 2 to itself udne","If I continue to add 2 to itself udn","If I continue to add 2 to itself ud","If I continue to add 2 to itself under 9, can I get every whoel","If I continue to add 2 to itself under 9, can I get every whoe","If I continue to add 2 to itself under 9, can I get every whole number in the ","If I continue to add 2  to itse lf under 9, can I get every whole number i","If I continue to add 2 to itself under 9, can I get every whole number ","If I continue to add 2 to itself under 9, can I get every whole number ","If I continue to add 2 to itself under 9, can I get every whole number? 2, 4, 6, 8, 1, 3, 5, 7, 9 = 0","If I continue to add 2 to itself under 9, can I get every whole number? 2, 4, 6, 8, 1, 3, 5, 7, 9 = ","If I continue to add 2 to itself under 9, can I get every whole number? 2, 4, 6, 8, 1, 3, 5, 7, 9 =","If I continue to add 2 to itself under 9, can I get every whole number? 2, 4, 6, 8, 1, 3, 5, 7, 9 ","If I continue to add 2 to itself under 9, can I get every whole number? 2, 4, 6, 8, 1, 3, 5, 7, 9","If I continue to add 2 to itself under 9, can I get every whole number? 2, 4, 6, 8, 1, 3, 5, 7, 0. Yes, I can"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":64365,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":555467,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3  a genera tor under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"If I continue to add 3 to itself under 9, can I get every whole number? 3, 6, 0, 3, 6, 0... No, I cannot.","explanation_history":["If I continue to add 3 tp ","If I continue to add 3 tp","If I continue to add 3 to itself une","If I continue to add 3 to itself under 9, can I get every whole number? 3 ","If I continue to add 3 to itself under 9, can I get every whole number? 3, 6, 9","If I continue to add 3 to itself under 9, can I get every whole number? 3, 6, 0, 3, 6, 0... n","If I continue to add 3 to itself under 9, can I get every whole number? 3, 6, 0, 3, 6, 0... No, I can not.","If I continue to add 3 to itself under 9, can I get every whole number? 3, 6, 0, 3, 6, 0... No, I cannot."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":24615,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":580083,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"If I continue to add 5 to itself under 9, can I get every whole number? 5, 1, 6, 2, 7, 3, 8, 4, 0, 5... Yes, I can!","explanation_history":["If I continue to add 56 ","If I continue to add 56","If I continue to add 5 to itsaelf u","If I continue to add 5 to itsaelf ","If I continue to add 5 to itsaelf","If I continue to add 5 to itsael","If I continue to add 5 to itsae","If I continue to add 5 to itsa","If I continue to add 5 to itself under 9, can I get every whol enu","If I continue to add 5 to itself under 9, can I get every whol en","If I continue to add 5 to itself under 9, can I get every whol e","If I continue to add 5 to itself under 9, can I get every whol ","If I continue to add 5 to  itself  under 9, can I get every whole numebr? ","If I continue to add 5 to itself under 9, can I get every whole numebr?","If I continue to add 5 to itself under 9, can I get every whole numebr","If I continue to add 5 to itself under 9, can I get every whole numeb","If I continue to add 5 to itself under 9, can I get every whole nume","If I continue to add 5 to itself under 9, can I get every whole number? 5, 1, 6, 2, 7, 3, 8, 4, 0, 5... Yes, I can!"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":37367,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":617451,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"If I continue to add 6 under 9, can I get every whole number? 6, 3, 0, 6, 3... No, I cannot.","explanation_history":["If Ic onti","If Ic ont","If Ic on","If  Ic o"," If Ic ","If Ic","If I cont","If I continue to add 6 under 9, can I get w","If I continue to add 6 under 9, can I get every whole number ?","If I continue to add 6 under 9, can I get every whole number ","If I continue to add 6 under 9, can I get every whole number? 6, 3, 9","If I continue to add 6 under 9, can I get every whole number? 6, 3, 0, 6, ","If I continue to add 6 under 9, can I get every whole number? 6, 3, 0, 6,","If I continue to add 6 under 9, can I get every whole number? 6, 3, 0, 6, 3... No, I cannot."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":31927,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":649379,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in f or the a rbitrary value if necessary.","rt":3248,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":652627,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"I = N - 1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["n ","n","N = ","N =","N + ","N +","N ","N","(N + 1 ","(N + 1)","(N","(","Inverse +","Inverse ","In","I + 1 = N, =","I + 1 = N, ","I + 1 = N, so N =","N","I = N-","I = N - 1"],"rt":37264,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":689892,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I = N - X","explain":true,"explanation":"Element X plus invers e I must  equal N, as N - N = 0 under N. So if X + I = N, then I = N - X","explanation_history":["X","The ","The","Th","T","Element X to I","Element X to ","Element X to","Element X t","Element X plus ivner","Element X plus ivne","Element X plus ivn","Element X plus iv","Element X plus inverse I must equal N, such that ","Element X plus inverse I must equal N, s","Element X plus inverse I must equal N, as N - n = ","Element X plus inverse I must equal N, as N - n =","Element X plus inverse I must equal N, as N - n ","Element X plus inverse I must equal N, as N - n","Element X plus inverse I must equal N, as N - N = 0 under N, ","Element X plus inverse I must equal N, as N - N = 0 under N,","Element X plus inverse I must equal N, as N - N = 0 under N. So if X + I = n","Element X plus inverse I must equal N, as N - N = 0 under N. So if X + I = N, then I = N - X"],"response_history":["X ","X","I = N -x","I = N - X"],"rt":46055,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":735947,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"N and X can have no common denominators","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["N and X can n","N and X can have no common denominators"],"rt":51039,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":786987,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":9441,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":796428,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":3120,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":799548,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":23688,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":823237,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a genera tor unde r +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"True","explain":true,"explanation":"Essentially, this means that X and N must have a common denominator. The definition of a generator X is that it has NO common denominators with N, thus this is true.","explanation_history":["Essentially,. t","Essentially,. ","Essentially,.","Essentially, this means taht ","Essentially, this means taht","Essentially, this means tah","Essentially, this means ta","Essentially, this means that X and N must have a common dden","Essentially, this means that X and N must have a common dde","Essentially, this means that X and N must have a common dd","Essentially, this means that X and N must have a common denominator for ","Essentially, this means that X and N must have a common denominator for","Essentially, this means that X and N must have a  common d enominator fo","Essentially, this means that X and N must have a common denominator f","Essentially, this means that X and N must have a common denominator ","Essentially, this means that X and N must have a common denominator. W","Essentially, this means that X and N must have a common denominator. The definition of a d","Essentially, this means that X and N must have a common denominator. The definition of a generator is that is h","Essentially, this means that X and N must have a common denominator. The definition of a generator is that is ","Essentially, this means that X and N must have a common denominator. The definition of a generator i","Essentially, this means that X and N must have a common denominator. The definition of a generator X is that it has NO common denoim","Essentially, this means that X and N must have a common denominator. The definition of a generator X is that it has NO common denoi","Essentially, this means that X and N must have a common denominat or. The  definition of a generator X is that it has NO common denominators with N, thus this is true."],"response_history":["False","True"],"rt":48468,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":871706,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":13224,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":884931,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always ","Somet imes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Sometimes","explain":true,"explanation":"If 1 is a generator under N, 1 + 1 = 2 is not necessarily a generator. However, if X is not equal to 1 and is a generator, X + X = 2X CAN be a generator. Thus, this is sometimes true.","explanation_history":["IF 1","IF ","IF","If 1 is a generator under N, i","If 1 is a generator under N, 1 + 1 = 2 d","If 1 is a generator under N, 1 + 1 = 2 is not necessarily a generator. However, if some non-1 ","If 1 is a generator under N, 1 + 1 = 2 is not necessarily a generator. However, if some no","If 1 is a generator under N, 1 + 1 = 2 is not necessarily a generator. However, if some n","If 1 is a generator under N, 1 + 1 = 2 is not necessarily a generator. However, if some gea","If 1 is a generator under N, 1 + 1 = 2 is not necessarily a generator. However, if some gena","If 1 is a generator under N, 1 + 1 = 2 is not necessarily a generator. However, if some gen","If 1 is a generator un der N, 1  + 1 = 2 is not necessarily a generator. However, if some ge","If 1 is a generator under N, 1 + 1 = 2 is not necessarily a generator. However, if some g","If 1 is a generator under N, 1 + 1 = 2 is not necessarily a generator. However, if some ","If 1 is a generator under N, 1 + 1 = 2 is not necessarily a generator. However, if some","If 1 is a generator under N, 1 + 1 = 2 is not necessarily a generator. However, if X is not equal to 1 and is a generator, X + X = 2x ","If 1 is a generator under N, 1 + 1 = 2 is not necessarily a generator. However, if X is not equal to 1 and is a generator, X + X = 2x","If 1 is a generator under N, 1 + 1 = 2 is not necessarily a generator. However, if X is not equal to 1 and is a generator, X + X = 2X CAN be a generator. Thus, this is sometimes true."],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":63863,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":948795,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is  not a ge nerator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes","Never"],"rt":13917,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":962715,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1158,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":963875,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"29","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["29"],"rt":2680,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":966555,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":1879,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":968434,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Differential Equations, Partial DiffEq, Number Theory, Graph Theory","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["D iffi","Differi","Differential Equatiosn, ","Differential Equatiosn,","Differential Equatiosn","Differential Equatios","Differential Equations, Parital D","Differential Equations, Parital ","Differential Equations, Parital","Differential Equations, Parita","Differential Equations, Parit","Differential Equations, Pari","Differential Equations, Partial DIf","Differential Equations, Partial DI","Differential Equations, Partial DiffEq with Bas","Differential Equations, Partial DiffEq ","Differential Equations, Partial DiffEq, Number Theory, Graph Theory"],"rt":31673,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1000108,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"5 - used it, remember and understand it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"rt":2822,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1002931,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"5 - used it, remember and understand it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"rt":2240,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1005172,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned  somethin g from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2815,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1007988,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":1968,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1009956,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3  - defin itely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":1551,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1011507,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Male"],"rt":1792,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1013300,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":3319,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1016619,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":2991,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1019611,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Great HIT! took me back to my days in school :) Thanks so much.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Great hit","Great hi","Great h","Great Hi","Great HIt","Great HIT! took me back to my days in school :) Thanks so much."],"rt":12255,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1031867,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]